{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Frequently used fuel gas in oxy-fuel welding is",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Acetylene",
        "b": "Biogas",
        "c": "Coal gas",
        "d": "Both (a) and (b) "
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"You are right",
        "b":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following flame types has more oxygen than acetylene?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Balanced flame",
        "b": "Oxygen-rich flame",
        "c": "Carbon-rich flame",
        "d": "None"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "b":"You are right",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },

  {
      "question": "How many different kinds of flames are used in gas welding?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "1",
        "b": "2",
        "c": "3",
        "d": "4"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer",
        "b":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer",
        "c":"You are right",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Which of the following flames is used to weld brass??",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Oxygen-rich flame",
        "b": "Carbon-rich flame",
        "c": "Balanced flame",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"You are right",
        "b":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Which gas cylinder has a permeable interior?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Acetylene Cylinder",
        "b": "Oxygen Cylinder",
        "c": "Both",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"You are right",
        "b":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "In the Oxyacetylene welding assembly, the colour of the acetylene cylinder is",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Blue",
        "b": "Black",
        "c": "Maroon",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer",
        "b":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer",
        "c":"You are right",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Which of the following flames has three zones?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Balanced flame",
        "b": "Carbon-rich flame",
        "c": "Oxygen-rich flame",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "b":"You are right",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "For joining and cutting, a neutral flame is used in",
      "answers": {
        "a": "All ferrous materials",
        "b": "All nonferrous materials",
        "c": "Both (a) and (b)",
        "d": "Brass"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer",
        "b":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer",
        "c":"You are right",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"c\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "Disadvantage of oxyacetylene welding is",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Costly and extremely unstable ",
        "b": "Easy to handle",
        "c": "the maximum temperature is produced ",
        "d": "None"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"You are right",
        "b":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"a\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
{
      "question": "What is the colour of the oxygen cylinder in the Oxyacetylene assembly?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Green",
        "b": "Black",
        "c": "Red",
        "d": "White"
      },
      "explanations":{ 
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "b":"You are right",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "A carburizing flame is suitable for welding",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Mild steel",
        "b": "high carbon steel",
        "c": "stainless steel",
        "d": "Cast iron"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "b":"You are right",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "The hottest part of the oxyacetylene flame is located in the",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Outer cone",
        "b": "Inner cone",
        "c": "Mixing zone",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "b":"You are right",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "An oxidizing flame is suitable for welding",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Low carbon steel",
        "b": "high carbon steel",
        "c": "Aluminium",
        "d": "Copper"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "b":"You are right",
        "c":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer",
        "d":"Your are Wrong, Option \"b\" is correct answer"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
]
}